<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Jetbird</title>
		<link>http://localhost/jetbird/</link>
		<description>The everyday problems of two geeks</description>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 20:35:10 +0200</lastBuildDate>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2009 20:57:08 +0200</pubDate>
		<generator>Jetbird 1.0</generator>
		<ttl>120</ttl>

		<item>
			<title>iPhone Dev 101: Creating Xcode projects, brief Xcode UI overview</title>
			<link>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=14</link>
			<description>In our last iPhone Dev 101, a continuing series on iPhone development, we talked about resources that you can use while you are coding with Cocoa. In this dev post, I'm going to walk you through Xcode and creating your first project.</description>
			<author>Victor</author>
			<comments>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=14#comments</comments>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 20:35:10 +0200</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Mobclix beefs up metrics, iPhone devs make money</title>
			<link>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=13</link>
			<description>Mobclix has been providing an impressive amount of usage information to iPhone developers for only about six months now, but have already made it into the 2008 TechCrunch 50, won SeedCamp 2008, and been recognized as a leading provider of metrics and analytics reporting.</description>
			<author>Victor</author>
			<comments>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=13#comments</comments>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 20:29:28 +0200</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>A different kind of Alarm Clock</title>
			<link>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=11</link>
			<description>We've reviewed some iPhone alarms before. There are free alarms and alarms you pay for. Some were pretty good, and there is always the built-in alarm. In an attempt to improve upon the standard alarms, some Russian developers have created Easy Wakeup [App Store link] which has been available for jailbroken phones, but now is available at U.</description>
			<author>Victor</author>
			<comments>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=11#comments</comments>
			<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 19:39:54 +0200</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>What's new in iPhoto 8.0.2</title>
			<link>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=10</link>
			<description>Last week, Apple released iLife updates with typically terse descriptions. Dissatisfied with &quot;...overall application stability improvements,&quot; I explored iPhoto 8.0.2 for obvious changes. Here's what I found.</description>
			<author>Victor</author>
			<comments>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=10#comments</comments>
			<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 18:43:54 +0200</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>The case for Applecare</title>
			<link>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=8</link>
			<description>With the holidays approaching, I know more than one family will be getting a new Mac. Many first time buyers whom I've guided through the purchase of their first Mac ask me, &quot;is AppleCare worth it?&quot;

For your new Mac, absolutely; I speak from first-hand experience.</description>
			<author>Victor</author>
			<comments>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=8#comments</comments>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 00:38:32 +0100</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Nvidia GeForce GTX 295 preview</title>
			<link>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=7</link>
			<description>Introduction

Nobody likes being second place, especially Nvidia. Back when the company launched its GeForce GTX 260 and 280 boards, AMD was huffing fumes with its Radeon HD 3870. Not surprisingly, the GT200-based gamer cards extended Nvidia's lead.</description>
			<author>Victor</author>
			<comments>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=7#comments</comments>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 00:35:59 +0100</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Beta Beat: BlackBerry Media Sync for OS X</title>
			<link>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=5</link>
			<description>Back in September, we started hearing rumblings that RIM was developing native OS X utilities for Mac BlackBerry users. Today, RIM has released a preview version of its BlackBerry Media Sync utility for OS X.</description>
			<author>Victor</author>
			<comments>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=5#comments</comments>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 00:29:52 +0100</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Rank and sales data could help figure out App Store popularity algorithm</title>
			<link>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=4</link>
			<description>Joel Comm, publisher of the highly-useful app iFart Mobile, has published some data about how sales related to popularity in the App Store.

While I have only a high-school understanding of statistics, it would appear from Comm's data that as sales rise in a linear fashion, App Store ranking increases (or I should say decreases, because lower numbers are better) logarithmically.</description>
			<author>Victor</author>
			<comments>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=4#comments</comments>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:16:10 +0100</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Talkcast tonight at 10 pm, last dance for 2008</title>
			<link>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=2</link>
			<description>Robert and Dave fought their way through a Talkshoe hardware failure to do a great talkcast last week, covering the concept of the 'kitchen Mac' and more. You can listen to the show from Talkshoe's site, or download the episode in iTunes / via RSS.</description>
			<author>Victor</author>
			<comments>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=2#comments</comments>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:15:27 +0100</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Beta Beat: Fontcase</title>
			<link>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=1</link>
			<description>A few months ago, a teaser appeared for a new Mac OS X font management app, Fontcase, developed by Pieter Omvlee and with an UI design by Laurent Baumann. Fontcase is designed to replace Apple's Font Book utility, which is not only a mediocre font management app, but has a less than nuanced interface.</description>
			<author>Victor</author>
			<comments>http://localhost/jetbird/?view&amp;id=1#comments</comments>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:15:08 +0100</pubDate>
		</item>

	</channel>
</rss>